package mongo // import "go.mongodb.org/mongo-driver/v2/mongo"

func Connect(opts ...*options.ClientOptions) (*Client, error)
    Connect creates a new Client with the given configuration options.

    Connect returns an error if the configuration options are invalid, but does
    not validate that the MongoDB deployment is reachable. To verify that the
    deployment is reachable, call Client.Ping.

    When creating an options.ClientOptions, the order the methods are called
    matters. Later option setter calls overwrite the values from previous
    option setter calls, including the ApplyURI method. This allows callers
    to determine the order of precedence for setting options. For instance,
    if ApplyURI is called before SetAuth, the Credential from SetAuth will
    overwrite the values from the connection string. If ApplyURI is called after
    SetAuth, then its values will overwrite those from SetAuth.

